pathtoim.com 2010-12-27

# InvisibleWealthSecret|Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

The statement below outlines our privacy policy.

TD Markketing LLP and it's subsidiaries collect personal information from you when you sign up.

TD Markketing LLP and it's subsidiaries will not sell, rent, share, trade, or give away your personal identifiable information without your consent first, unless required by law, to any third party. Any information that we obtain is held securely and protected.

We can, and you authorize us to, disclose personal information to local, regional, state or federal law enforcement officials when required to do so by public authorities or when we believe in good faith that law requires it.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,  [ click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the  [ DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Copyright © TD Markketing LLP. All Rights Reserved.
